Guide to the Women's Refugee Commission Records, 1979-2020; 1979-ongoing, bulk 1989-2011 RL.01405
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Executive Director Files Series, 5 boxes
  - Carolyn Makinson
    - Passman, Pamela, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Paung, Shah, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Nancy Pereczman, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Advocacy Day and Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., March 12, 2008 (Box 51)
    - General Board Comms., 2005 (Box 51)
    - Exec. Committee Meeting, Pre-October 2005 (Box 51)
    - Executive Comm., 5/05 (Box 51)
  - Sarah Costa
    - Liv Ullmann, Honorary chair, 1999-2013 (Box 52)
    - Liv, 2009-2016 (2 folders) (Box 52)
- Board of Directors (BOD) Files Series
  The Board of Directors (BOD) Files Series contains primarily board member packets and planning documents for Commission board meetings between 1997-2014. Some board member packets also contain Advocacy Day materials. There are also items related to the Excecutive and Nominating Committee meetings, as well as packets on specialized topics, such as peace initiatives and the Bureau of Public Affairs in the U.S. Department of State. There are a few files related to Board mailings, donors, and potential commissioners.
  Boxes 57-59 in this series are from Accession 2016-0110.
  - WRC Board Meeting, October 25, 2014 (Box 57)
  - WRC Board Meeting, May 2, 2014 (Box 57)
  - WRC Board Meeting, October 25-26, 2013 (Box 57)
  - WRC Board Meeting, May 3, 2012 (Box 57)
  - WRC Board Meeting, October 28-29, 2011 (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - WRC Board Meeting, May 3-4, 2011 (Box 57)
  - Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children (WCRWC) Board Meeting, October 18, 2002 (Box 57)
  - IRC BOD Annual Meeting, February 16, 2011 (Box 57)
  - WRC Luncheon, May 6, 2010 (Box 57)
  - WRC Board Meeting, October 23, 2009 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Board Folder Template, October 2005 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, October 2005 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Template, Advocacy Day, March 2005 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Reference Folder, March 2005 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Board Meeing, 12 May 2005 (Box 57)
  - Board Meeting and Advocacy Day, 16 March 2005 (Box 57)
  - New Board Members Folders, 2005 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Board Orientation, October 13, 2006 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC New York Advocacy and the United Nations, 9 March 2006 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC The Plight of Children in INS Custody..., undated (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Advocacy Day, February 2001? (Box 57)
  - October 2001 Board Meeting (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, October 19-20, 2001 (Box 57)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, June 4, 2001 (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, February 24, 2001 (Box 57)
  - Board Mtg & Advocacy Day, February 2001 (Box 57)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, 10 May 2007 (2 folders) (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, 20 March 2007 (Box 58)
  - BOD October 12, 2007 (Box 58)
  - Cynthia Galik, Board Meeting, March 20, 2007 (Box 58)
  - U.S. Department of State, Bureau of Public Affairs folder, 2006-2007 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Delegation Draft Itinerary, July 10-12, 2007 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, 6 May 2008 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, October 2008 (Box 58)
  - Women's Commission Advocacy Day/Board Meeting, February 26, 2003 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting and Advocacy Day, February 26, 2003 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, May 15, 2003 (2 folders) (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, October 18, 2003 (Box 58)
  - Board Meeting, May 2005 (Box 58)
  - Board Meeting Planning, 2004-2005 (2 folders) (Box 58)
  - Board Meeting, May 2002 (Box 58)
  - Board Meeting/Advocacy Day, March 12, 2002 (Box 58)
  - Memos (Board of Directors 2002) (Box 58)
  - Board Meeting/Advocacy Day, February 25, 2004 (Box 58)
  - Board Meeting, October 18, 2003 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting 16 October 2004 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, 13 May 2004 (3 folders) (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, 15 May 2002 (Box 58)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, October 19, 2002 (Box 58)
  - Excomm, 2008 (Box 58)
  - ExCom, Feb 6, 2008 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, September 24, 2007 (Box 58)
  - Executive Committee, April 19, 2007 (Box 58)
  - Nominating Lunch, April 11, 2008 (Box 58)
  - Anne Tatlock, 2007 (Box 58)
  - Potential Board Members & Commissioners, 2007 (Box 58)
  - Nominating Committee, 2007 (Box 58)
  - Nominating Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 58)
  - Commissioner Terms, 2008 and undated (Box 58)
  - Board Management, 2005 (Box 58)
  - Requests for Aid Abroad, 2009 (Box 58)
  - Food Crisis/WFP, 2008 (Box 58)
  - Resettlement, 2009 (Box 58)
  - Board Meeting, March 7, 1998 (Box 58)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, May 13, 1998 (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, June 4, 2001 (Box 59)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, 15 May 2002 (Box 59)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, October 19-20, 2001 (Box 59)
  - February Board Meeting, 2001 (Box 59)
  - Board Correspondence, 2001 (Box 59)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, October 18, 2002 (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, February 24, 2001 (Box 59)
  - Woment's Commission Board Meeting, May 13, 1999 (Box 59)
  - Board Meeting, February 1999 (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, February 20, 1999 (Box 59)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, February 25, 2000 (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, June 6, 2000 (Box 59)
  - Board/Donors, 1995 (Box 59)
  - Board Mailings, 1998 (Box 59)
  - Board, General, 1995, 1998 (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, September 19, 1998 (Box 59)
  - Mary Diaz Tributes, 2004 (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission tribute to Mary Diaz, 2004; 1 digital file extractd from an optical disc; approximately 132 megabytes (Digital-materials RL01405-SET-0004, Disk RL01405-OP-0006)
    Includes tribute video created following Diaz' death, mpeg file format.
  - Mary Diaz photograph, 2005; 1 digital file extracted from an optical disc; approximately 53 kilobytes (Digital-materials RL01405-SET-0004, Disk RL01405-OP-0009)
    Includes one color photograph of Diaz writing; file modified in 2005. Jpeg file format.
  - Mary Diaz portrait, 2004; 1 dgital file extracted from an optical disc; approximately 8 megabytes (Digital-materials RL01405-SET-0004, Disk RL01405-OP-0010)
    Inludes one color portrait of Diaz, tiff file format.
  - Photographs of Mary Diaz, 2001-2003; 6 digital files extracted from an optical disc; approximately 2 megabytes (Digital-materials RL01405-SET-0004, Disk RL01405-OP-0011)
    Includes six photographs, five color, one black-and-white, of Diaz alone or with others. Jpeg file format.
  - Board Meeting, March 7, 1997 (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, September 27, 1997 (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - Board of Directors meeting, May 15, 1997 (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - Board Meeting, March 1, 1997 (Box 59)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, March 7, 1998 (Box 59)
  - WCRWC Board Meeting, 6 May 2008 (Box 59)
  - Board Finance and Development Committee, 2000 (Box 59)
  - Board Mailing for September 6, 2000 (Box 59)
  - Op-Ed Pieces, 1999 and undated (Box 59)
  - Board Peace Task Force, 1999 and undated (Box 59)
  - Board Meeting, September 1999 (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, September 17, 1999 (Box 59)
  - Women's Commission Board Meeting, February 20, 1999 (Box 59)
  - WCRWC Mary Diaz Group 1, 1999 and undated (Box 59)
  - Board Planning Documents, 1998-1999 and undated (Box 59)
- Washington, D.C. Office Files Series, 1992-2006, 6 boxes
  The material in this accession was received from the Women's Refugee Commission's Washington, D.C. office, the location of their Detention and Asylum Program (DAP). DAP works to ensure that vulnerable migrants in the United States are not detained unless absolutely necessary and that their basic rights are protected and respected. DAP advocates for legislation and policy that would ensure the safety and well-being of migrant women, families and unaccompanied children. DAP works with the executive branch, the U.S. Congress and the Department of Homeland Security, including its various agencies, to institutionalize these important safeguards.
  This series has been loosely sorted into six sub-series: Children, Detention and Asylum, Gender, INS, Haiti, and Other. The Children sub-series contains a wide range of material, including drafts and debates surrounding the Unaccompanied Alien Children Protection Act; files on child soldiers; and reports on refugee children. The Detention and Asylum sub-series contains the largest amount of materials, and includes files on specific detention facilities; asylum laws, policies, and reports; and advocacy and media initiatives. Gender files encompass numerous aspects of issues relating to women, including health, domestic violence, trafficking, and sexual assault. INS materials largely relate to the WRC's interactions with various INS officers and agencies, as well as conditions at various INS-run facilities.
  Due to its size, the Haiti sub-series has been sorted independently from the other sub-series. It includes reports, presentations, and internal files regarding Haiti refugees in particular, including children, detention facilities, human rights conditions, legal cases, and many other subjects which could easily fall into other sub-series.
  The D.C. Office Files are CLOSED for 20 years (until 2031), except to those individuals receiving prior permission from the donor. contact the Rubenstein Library with questions.
  - Children
    - Alone in America article, 2005 (Box 42)
    - Juvenile Docket Issues (Box 42)
    - Lee Otis and Esther Olavarria memo, 2000 Jan. 31 (Box 42)
    - Expedited Removal, kids (Box 42)
    - Unaccompanied Alien Children Protection Act: Government Suggested Changes, 2005 (Box 42)
    - Executive Office for Immigration Review (EOIR) Draft Guidelines, 2004 (Box 42)
    - Kids Video, 2005 (Box 42)
    - Children's Right to Counsel (Box 42)
    - Seeking Asylum Alone: Bethany Christian Services (Box 42)
    - Age Determination Examination (Box 42)
    - Children: Graca Machel Report (Box 42)
    - Children: Graca Machel Report, Impact of Armed Conflict on Children (Box 42)
    - Children: Graca Machel Report, Conference and Notes (Box 42)
    - Children: Graca Machel Report, Zones of Peace (Box 42)
    - Children: Task Force on Refugee Children (Box 42)
    - Feinstein, 2005 Mar. (Box 42)
    - Dental Cases (Box 42)
    - Temporary Protected Services Kids - Detention (Box 42)
    - S121 Minors Bill (Box 42)
    - Amicus Brief, 11th Circle - Elian Gonzalez (Box 42)
    - Notice to Children (Box 42)
    - Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR)/EOID Pilot Part II, 2003 (Box 42)
    - S.1129 Press Conference, 2003 (Box 42)
    - ORR Implementation, 2003 (Box 42)
    - Alfredo Court Transcript, 1997-2002 (Box 42)
    - Berks City Youth Center, 1995 (Box 42)
    - Liberty and Medina Cities/LCCR (Box 42)
    - Early Drafts-S.121 - Alien Children Protection Act, 2000 (Box 42)
    - Flores Proposed Rule (Box 42)
    - General: Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR) (Box 42)
    - Children: Background (Box 42)
    - Feinstein Draft of UACPA, 2003 Nov. (Box 42)
    - Kids Bill (Box 42)
    - Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR) Age Determination Policy (Box 42)
    - Special Immigrant Juvenile (SIJ) Sign-on Letter (Box 42)
    - Unaccompanied Children (Box 42)
    - Afghanistan Research (Box 42)
    - Carr Project Background (Box 42)
    - Harvard Project (Box 42)
    - Task Force on Refugee Children (Box 42)
    - British Refugee Council report on refugee children (Box 42)
    - United Kingdom Children Advisers (Box 42)
    - Children: Unaccompanied Children (Box 42)
    - European Union Paper on Displaced Children (Box 42)
    - Child Asylum Legislation, Feinstein S.121 (Box 42)
    - Child Detention Trip, 2001 Aug. (Box 42)
    - Issues: Children (Box 42)
    - Issues: Children, Great Lakes Region, Research, 1997 Fall (Box 42)
    - Kids' Facilities, 2004 Dec. (Box 42)
    - Juvenile Statistics, 1994 (Box 42)
    - Canadian Children Guidelines (Box 42)
    - Children: France (Box 42)
    - Flores Regulation Response (Box 42)
    - Children's Questionnaire (Box 42)
    - Europe: Child Asylum (Box 42)
    - S. 3117-106th C. (S. 121) (Box 43)
    - S. 121 Written Testimony (Box 43)
    - USCR Meeting (Box 43)
    - Children: Child Soldiers (Box 43)
    - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF): Children in Armed Conflict (Box 43)
    - Working Group on Children in Armed Conflict, Administration (Box 43)
    - Working Group on Children in Armed Conflict, International Criminal Court (Box 43)
    - Working Group on Children in Armed Conflict, Special Representative Olara Otunnu (Box 43)
    - Working Group on Children in Armed Conflict, Child Soldiers/Optional Protocol (Box 43)
    - Children: UNICEF NGO Committee, Working Group on Children in Armed Conflict (Box 43)
    - Children: NGO Working Group on Children, Quaker House Group (Box 43)
    - World Bank Proposal, Adolescent, 1999 (Box 43)
    - Roundtable Background Material: Children (Box 43)
    - UNICEF/NGO Working Group on Children in Armed Conflict (Box 43)
    - Children's Task Force (Box 43)
    - Issues: Children, Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Children: UNICEF/NGO Committee Working Group on Children in Armed Conflict (Box 43)
    - UNICEF Guidelines letter (Box 43)
    - Harvard Children's Project (Box 43)
    - Jackson-Lee Bill (Box 43)
    - Unaccompanied Alien Child Protection Act of 2004 (Box 43)
  - Detention and Asylum
    - Operation Compliance (Box 43)
    - Expedited Removal, 2005 Nov. (Box 43)
    - Interception (Box 43)
    - United Nations Working Group on Arbitrary Detention (Box 43)
    - International Coalition on Detention (Box 43)
    - Vulnerable Populations Detention Legislation (Box 43)
    - Detention: Advocacy Day 1997 Follow-Up (Box 43)
    - Detention: Congressional Members Information (Box 43)
    - Detention: Krome Detention Center (Box 43)
    - Liberty Denied: Women Seeking Asylum Imprisoned in the United States (Box 43)
    - Detention: Advocacy Day 1997 Handouts (Box 43)
    - Detention: Elizabeth, New Jersey Facility (Box 43)
    - Detention: Carbondale, Illinois (Box 43)
    - Tri-County Detention Facility, Ullin, Illinois (Box 43)
    - Domestic Delegation, Esmor, Elizabeth, New Jersey (Box 43)
    - Turner Guilford Knight Correctional Center (TGK) Detention Report (Krome Follow-Up) (Box 43)
    - Detention: Washington D.C. Meetings, 1997 Apr. (Box 43)
    - Detention Watch Network News (Box 43)
    - York County Prison Report, 1998 Jul. (Box 43)
    - Detention: Publication, Locks on the Golden Door (Box 43)
    - Turner Guilford Knight Correctional Center (TGK) (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Detention Statistics, 1997-1998 (Box 43)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) Detention Press Release, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) Detention Report, 1996 (Box 44)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) Detention Report, 1998 (Box 44)
    - Pearson Memo on Detention, 1998 (Box 44)
    - Appropriation's Detention Victory, 2005 (Box 44)
    - Detention (Box 44)
    - Testimony on Detention Bill (Box 44)
    - Los Pudrinos, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Wyrsch Memo regarding sanitary supplies for refugees (Box 44)
    - Department of Homeland Security Alternatives to Detention (Box 44)
    - Excom Detection, 1999 Oct. (Box 44)
    - Liberty Shield (Box 44)
    - United Nations Standard Minimum Rules for Treatment of Prisoners (Box 44)
    - David Joseph Case (Box 44)
    - Judith Kumin - Interdiction (Box 44)
    - Detention Watch Network (DWN) (Box 44)
    - Detention Watch Network (DWN) Advocacy Day, 2005 (Box 44)
    - Detention Watch Network (DWN) (Box 44)
    - Detention: Wackenhut Detention Facility, Directions to Wackenhut (Box 44)
    - Domestic Detention: Wackenhut Visit, 1997 Nov. 21 (Box 44)
    - Adelaide Abankwak-Ghana, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - AILA v. Reno (DC Circuit Expedited Removal Decision) (Box 44)
    - Other S.121 Testimony (Box 44)
    - Minimum Initial Services Package (MISP) (Box 44)
    - Detention and Asylum Project (DAP) Objectives, 2003 (Box 44)
    - Aicha Garba (Box 44)
    - Expedited Removal Amicus Brief (Box 44)
    - Varick Street Service Processing Center (Box 44)
    - Detention: Media, 1998 (Box 44)
    - Detention: Media Coverage (Box 44)
    - Detention: Media, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Detention: Report Background (Box 44)
    - Domestic Delegation: Media (Box 44)
    - Detention: Legislation (Box 44)
    - Detention: Litigation Reform (Box 44)
    - Detention: Amicus Brief (Box 44)
    - Detention: Orrick, Herrington, and Sutcliffe, LLP (Box 44)
    - Detention: Research (Box 44)
    - Domestic Delegation (Box 44)
    - Statements/Interviews (Box 44)
    - York County Prison (Box 44)
    - Detention: Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) Guidelines for Children's Asylum Claims (Box 44)
    - York County Prison, 1998 Jul. 22 (Box 44)
    - Detention and Asylum: Expedited Removal Study, International Human Rights and Migration Project, California (Box 44)
    - Aquadilla Service Processing Center, Puerto Rico (Box 44)
    - INS Detention: Bakersfield, CA (Box 44)
    - Detention: Chicago (Box 44)
    - New York Advocacy (Box 44)
    - Detention Project: Meetings/Advocacy (Box 45)
    - Real ID, 2005 (Box 45)
    - Senate Testimony, 1998 Sept. (Box 45)
    - Detention Facility List, 2003 (Box 45)
    - Abraham Bill (Box 45)
    - Ankle Bracelets (Box 45)
    - United Kingdom/United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) 3 Prong (Box 45)
    - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) Guidelines Revision (Box 45)
    - Guidelines Revision (Box 45)
    - Evaluation Follow-up (Box 45)
    - Statement on Interdiction, 2000 Jun. (Box 45)
    - Asylum-Seekers in Detention: 41 Case Examples (Box 45)
    - Locking Up Family Values: The Detention of Immigration Families, 2007 Feb. 22 (Box 45)
    - Detention (Box 45)
    - Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR) Benefits for Asylees (Box 45)
    - Prosecution of Asylum Seekers in Florida (Box 45)
    - Florida Criminal Prosecution (Box 45)
    - Brownback Asylum (Box 45)
    - MPSG Proposed Regulations (Box 45)
    - Draft of MPSG Proposed Regulations, Gail Pendleton's Response (Box 45)
    - Senate Hearing and Testimonies, 1998 (Box 45)
    - Reorganization of the Department of Homeland Security (DHS), 2002 (Box 45)
    - IJ Decision (Box 45)
    - Temporary Protected Services (TPS) (Box 45)
    - AILA vs. Janet Reno (Box 45)
    - Swedish Asylum Law regarding gender (Box 45)
    - Family-Berks Center (Box 45)
    - Asylum Statistics (Box 45)
    - Phoenix Pilot Project (Box 45)
    - Proposed Parole Authorization Regulation (Box 45)
    - APSO memo, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Tulsky IJ Articles (Box 45)
    - Olowo case, 2004 (Box 45)
    - United States Asylum Policy (Box 45)
    - Kennedy Legislation (Box 45)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) Files
    - Becraft Declaration (Box 45)
    - Appointed/Pro bono (General) Counsel (Box 45)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) Cases (Box 45)
    - R-A Decision and Executive Order, 2001 (Box 45)
    - Department of Homeland Security Civil Rights and Civil Liberties Protection Act (Box 45)
    - Feinstein Document Fraud (Box 45)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service Propaganda (Box 45)
    - Kenn-Robb Billon Costs and Backgrounders (Box 45)
    - Approps Accomplishments, 2006 (Box 45)
    - S.121 Immigration and Naturalization Services Comments (Box 45)
    - Misuse of Alternatives Funding (Box 45)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) on Kids Detention (Box 45)
    - Docket Transfer (Box 45)
    - Wicomico, Maryland: Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) Correspondence (Box 45)
    - York County Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) Correspondence (Box 45)
  - Gender
    - Gender-based Asylum (Box 45)
    - Gender and Refugee Status Determination (Box 45)
    - Guatemalan Domestic Violence (Box 45)
    - Trafficking Letter to Leavitt, 2006 Jan. 3 (Box 45)
    - University of New South Wales (UNSW) Women at Risk (Box 45)
    - Research Information regarding R-A (Box 45)
    - Women at Risk (Box 45)
    - R-A- (Box 45)
    - Canada-Ward Decision (Box 45)
    - Roundtable on Gender Persecution (Box 45)
    - R-A- Congressional Response (Box 45)
    - R-A- Roundtable Minutes (Box 45)
    - R-A- Attorney General Certification (Box 45)
    - R-A- Practice Pointers and Decision (Box 45)
    - R-A- Amicus Brief, 2004 Feb. (Box 46)
    - Canada: Gender Guidelines (Box 46)
    - R-A-, 2003 (Box 46)
    - R-A- Media (Box 46)
    - R-A-: Media, Analysis, Decision (Box 46)
    - Women at Risk House Subcommittee Hearing on Torture Victims, 1996 May 8 (Box 46)
    - Roundtable Background Material: Domestic Violence (Box 46)
    - Roundtable Background Material: Sexual Assault (Box 46)
    - Roundtable Background Material: Sexual Orientation (Box 46)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) Gender Guidelines, 1995 May (Box 46)
    - Guidelines Correspondence (Box 46)
    - Guidelines for Women Asylum Claims, Beasley (Box 46)
    - Gender Based Persecution Asylum Cases (Box 46)
    - Report on Trafficking (Box 46)
    - Trafficking Report (Box 46)
    - Amendment to H.R. 10 (Box 46)
    - Trafficking Law Resource Guide (Box 46)
    - Guidelines (Box 46)
    - Anti-Prostitution Directive (Box 46)
    - FIAC Probono Room (Box 46)
    - Combating Trafficking Children for Sexual Purposes (Box 46)
  - Files relating to Haiti
    - Boat, 2002 Oct. (Box 46)
    - Dept. of Justice Decision, 2003 Apr. 17 (Box 46)
    - Haiti, 2004 (Box 46)
    - Haiti, 2004 (Box 46)
    - Haiti and Asylum Seeks: A Chronology of Major Events, 1971-1994 (Box 46)
    - Florida Immigrant Advocacy Center (FIAC) Senate Test, 2002 (Box 46)
    - Interdiction Statistics, 1982-1993 (Box 46)
    - Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children Briefing, 2002 Oct. (Box 46)
    - Bond Denials, 2002 (Box 46)
    - Congresswoman Ros-Lehtinen 7 Questions Department of State Response, 2002 (Box 46)
    - Senate Hearing, 2002 Oct. (Box 46)
    - Haitian Boat, 2001 Dec. (Box 46)
    - BOAT, 2001 Dec. (Box 46)
    - December Boatload (Box 46)
    - Children (Box 46)
    - Haitian Human Rights Report, 2005 (Box 46)
    - Interdiction Law Articles (Box 46)
    - Comfort Suites Hotel detention, 2003 (Box 46)
    - Press Release re: Haitian refugees, 2003 (Box 46)
    - Haitian Resettlement (Box 46)
    - Team Notes, 2002 (Box 46)
    - Haiti Presentations, 2005 (Box 46)
    - Dominican Republic/Haiti (Box 46)
    - Dominican Republic Background (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Barry University (Box 46)
    - Turner Guilford Knight Correctional Center (TGK) (Box 46)
    - Coast Guard Statistics (Box 46)
    - House Briefing: International Operations and Human Rights, 2002 (Box 46)
    - Church World Service Conference, 2003 Feb. (Box 46)
    - FIAC Background (1 of 2 folders) (Box 46)
    - FIAC Background (2 of 2 folders) (Box 47)
    - Refugee Protection Act Original (Box 47)
    - Haiti Background (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - American Immigration Lawyers Association (AILA) Report on Haiti, 2002 (Box 47)
    - Broward County Work Release Center (WRC) (Box 47)
    - Parole Memo from Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS) (Box 47)
    - Interdiction Order (Box 47)
    - Expedited Removal Order (Box 47)
    - Returnees (Box 47)
    - FICA Background (Box 47)
    - Haiti Research, 2004-2005 (Box 47)
    - Haiti News and Notes, 2004-2005 (Box 47)
    - Haiti - DJ (Box 47)
    - Haiti Op-Ed Letter, 2006 Jan. 11 (Box 47)
    - Kennedy Letters from the Department of Justice (Box 47)
    - Human Rights Watch (HRW) Rape Report (Box 47)
    - Cheryl Little article in University of Miami Law Review, 1999 Jul. (Box 47)
    - Guantanamo Bay Children, 1995 (Box 47)
    - Organization of American States Report, 2002 (Box 47)